https://digimania.be/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
–
Digimania (Urban Developments S.A.)
Address:
Chaussee de Ruisbroek/Steenweg op Ruisbroek 257
Drogenbos, 1620 Belgium
Mail: info@digimania.be
Phone: +32 2 5344611
TVA N°:  BE0436491288
Contact
Address:
Chaussee de Ruisbroek/Steenweg op
Ruisbroek 257 Drogenbos, 1620
Belgium
Phone: +32 2 8806041
Email: info@digimania.be
Website: www.digimania.be
We Accept
Nous utilisons des cookies pour vous garantir la meilleure expérience sur notre site. Si vous continuez à utiliser ce dernier, nous considérerons que vous acceptez l'utilisation des cookies.OkEn savoir plus
